The field of Machine Learning and Deep Learning is changing pretty rapidly.
机器学习和深度学习领域的发展瞬息万变
It's like a lot of research,
这个行业
a lot of applications in industry,
有很多研究和应用
and I wonder SageMaker is part of that.
SageMaker 也不例外
There's new features that are released pretty often,
非常频繁地发布新功能
very often as a matter of fact.
实际上太频繁了
I wonder within an internal team,
我想知道 作为内部员工
how do you decide on what features to work on?
你是如何判断要开发哪些功能的？
Traditionally at Amazon overall, Amazon Web Services,
一直以来 整个公司（包括 AWS）
we aggressively listen to our customers.
都积极聆听客户的需求
So we worked with customers and in essentially work backwards from what they need,
我们与客户合作 并反向满足他们的需求
and we've done that very successfully with different other products.
这种模式使很多其他产品也极为成功
If you think about what we've done with databases,
例如我们的数据库
or if you think about what we've done with compute with Amazon EC2,
Amazon EC2 计算功能
or if you think about what we've done with the Hadoop ecosystem,
Hadoop 生态系统
making Spark available on top of Amazon Elastic MapReduce.
Amazon Elastic MapReduce 之上的 Spark
The guiding principle behind all of these products was to listen to the market,
所有这些产品的指导原则都是聆听市场的需求
listen to customers internally and externally,
聆听内外部客户的需求
and trying to find out what would customers need or
并了解客户的需求是什么
what would add the most value to customers at a specific point in time.
以及在特定时间什么功能对客户的价值最大
So that's really how the road map is identified.
这就是规划蓝图的制定方式
Ninety to 95 percent of a road map is identified by talking to customers,
有 90-95% 的规划蓝图都是与客户沟通后确立的
and that's part of my job,
我的工作就是与客户沟通
and understanding what they want at a certain point in time,
了解在特定时间他们的需求是什么
and then bring that back to the product.
然后在产品中满足这些需求
We also do have some insights from working with internal customers
我们还从内部客户那获得反馈
like Alexa, or Amazon.com.
例如 Alexa 或 Amazon.com
So we learn a lot from their needs,
我们从他们的需求那学到了很多
and then base on those needs and combining that with our external customers needs,
并将他们的需求与外部客户的需求结合到一起
we can come up with a healthy road map.
制定一个强大的规划蓝图
In the back end, SageMaker has a very very large team.
在后台 SageMaker 有一个非常非常庞大的团队
We do have engineers that are focusing on optimizing TensorFlow, for example.
例如 我们有专门优化 TensorFlow 的工程师
We do have engineers that are focusing on optimizing Pytorch,
也有专门优化 Pytorch 的工程师
and then these folks work directly with
这些工程师与开源社区直接合作
the open source community and they contribute back to the code base of TensorFlow,
并为 TensorFlow Pytorch 或 MXnet
or Pytorch, or MXnet,
贡献代码
or all these Deep Learning Machine Learning frameworks.
或为所有这些深度学习和机器学习框架贡献代码
So there are large teams with very clear focuses,
这些大型团队的侧重点很清晰
and some of them are focusing on platform and infrastructure automation.
有些人负责平台和基础设施自动化
Some of them are focusing on Deep Learning algorithms,
有些负责深度学习算法
some of them are focusing on workflow and integration.
有些负责工作流程和集成
So it's a very large ecosystem of people that
这是一个很庞大的生态系统
are aggressively listening to customers and trying to
大家积极聆听客户的需求
find out what to build to meet the demand.
并了解为了满足这种需求 需要打造什么样的功能
Is there a feature among all of these that you find the most exciting right now,
在所有这些功能当中 你认为目前哪个功能最让你激动？
or maybe something you'd like to see in the future?
或者你希望未来能够实现什么功能？
Yeah. So if you think about the process that we just went through,
嗯回忆下我们刚刚学习的课程
I think when people talk about Machine Learning nowadays,
我认为如今当人们讨论机器学习时
one thing that we get to talk a lot about is the algorithm,
经常讨论的是算法
the Jupyter notebooks, and then training Machine Learning model.
Jupyter notebook 以及训练机器学习模型
But where's the data coming from?
但是数据是从哪来的？
How does the data get ready for Machine Learning model?
如何让数据为机器学习模型做好准备？
The very first step, yeah.
这是第一步
Right. So, I mean,
是的所以
in the industry there's this joke that goes about what is a data
在业内有个笑话
scientists spend 80 percent of their time cleaning the data,
数据科学家花费 80% 的时间清理数据
and 20 percent of their time.
有20% 的时间
Modeling and training a model, yeah.
建模和训练模型
Complaining about the data.
抱怨数据
So the idea really is to facilitate.
我们急需便于清理数据的流程
So one of the things that we spent a lot of energy on
去年 我们花费了大量精力
last year was to facilitate the process
开发能帮助简化这个流程的功能
of collecting the data and then creating real features,
从收集数据 到创建真实特征
or label training data out of raw data.
或从原始数据中提取训练数据
So if you want to create a computer vision algorithm for object detection,
如果你要创建对象检测计算机视觉算法
or a sentiment analysis like a classification on text algorithm,
或者是文本分类等情感分析算法
you probably want to have an initial set of clean data that real humans have looked at.
则需要人工查看过的初始整洁数据集
In the case of images,
对于图像来说
they would put bounding boxes around birds and then label that as birds,
已经有人在鸟类周围画上边界框并标为鸟类
around cars and label that as cars.
在汽车周围画上边界框 并标为汽车
So that ecosystem could be improved.
这个生态系统可以改进
So we did release a product at the end of last year called Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth,
我们在去年底推出了一款产品 叫做 Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth
that really helps with collecting real data,
这款工具可以极大地帮助我们
raw dataset from the real-world,
从真实世界里收集原始数据集
and creating a distributed task that goes out
并制定分布式任务
to either a public workforce of real humans that can help you create your features,
请公众帮助你创建特征
or a private workforce of potentially your staff or people with specialized skill set,
或者请有特殊技能的专门人士
like medical doctors that would be able to
例如医生可以识别医疗影像中的对象
recognize medical images and then annotate that accurately.
然后准确地标注
Really automate that entire ecosystem of targeting real people with raw data,
使整个生态系统自动化 包括向真实人员发送原始数据
getting their help about with labeling the data,
邀请他们标记数据
and eventually creating cleaned-up labeled data for the process of Machine Learning,
最终为机器学习创建整洁的带标签数据
and that's really the beginning.
这才是真正的第一步
Because before you start looking at the algorithms,
因为在查看算法 Jupyter notebook 之前
the Jupyter notebook, you really need to have a clean dataset.
非常需要一个整洁的数据集
So we innovated towards the end of last year,
我们在去年底经过创新
created Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth.
终于推出了 Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth
I'm not allowed to have a favorite,
我不应该偏袒于任何产品的
but that's one of my favorite products part of that entire ecosystem.
但在整个生态系统中 这是我最喜欢的产品之一
So you could as a user take
作为用户
personal photos or something and then send
你可以将个人照片等发送给亲友
them out to your family to label like what is your favorite thing,
请他们标记出最喜欢的事物
and then maybe try to learn where to
然后尝试规划
plan like the next best vacation. There's something in there?
下个最佳假期应该去哪类似于这样的
Yeah. You could do that.
是的可以这么做